<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Amelia Thornheart - Royal Road</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart</link><description>Chapter updates for Amelia Thornheart</description><item><title>Chapter One: The Vengeance</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1762434/chapter-one-the-vengeance</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1762434/chapter-one-the-vengeance</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 10:52:06 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[The first thing Amelia noticed upon waking was the lack of pain. She had become so used to either the rotting ache of her disease or the sharp pain of needles that she had forgotten what it felt like to not be in some form of agony. Her body felt floaty and warm and her mind, normally racked with exhaustion and headaches, felt clear and rested. Amelia set about trying to memorize these feelings she had long forgotten. After a few moments, she decided to risk flexing a few toes and found with delight this didn’t cause shooting pains. She moved a leg, and then an arm, and then deciding to risk it all, did something she hadn’t been able to do in years. “Mmmmmtth!” She stretched like a cat, feeling the satisfaction rivet through her body. Surely she had died and this was heaven! Although, she was definitely lying on a hard wooden floor and that didn’t seem very heaven-like at all. Not that she was complaining, compared to her years in the hospital a floor like this was welcome. Even so, sh...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Two: A Human Speaker!?</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1763021/chapter-two-a-human-speaker</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1763021/chapter-two-a-human-speaker</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 18:48:57 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“Forty-nine… fifty!” Amelia finished her last set of push-ups and sat up. It felt so good to move her body! How many years had it been since she had done a push-up? A squat? Was exercise always this enjoyable? Those foolish demons, they thought these thick chains on her hands and legs would restrict her! Rather they had given her ample opportunity for some resistance training! She was amazed at how her high base stats and ward had already translated into such strength and endurance. Amelia could tell the chains on her were heavy , no doubt designed to seriously slow down any fast movement or escape attempt, however, she found it remarkably easy to move around. Her cell was no more than a two-meter by two-meter box of iron bars that extended from the floor to the ceiling. It was one of a line of cells that were arranged in the center of this deck of the ship, but Amelia’s was the only one occupied. Hundreds of cargo crates and barrels lined the walls, with just enough space left for the...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Three: Battlestations</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1764590/chapter-three-battlestations</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1764590/chapter-three-battlestations</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:44:47 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“Captain on deck!” a voice rang out and everyone in the bridge scrambled to stand at attention. Serena took her position overlooking her loyal officers. The bridge was a cone-shaped room poking out the top of the Vengeance’s rear structure. It was ringed with thick reinforced windows for observation, through which Serena could see the three twin-barrel cannons lining the deck of the ship. Each cannon could fire a set of four-inch flak, explosive, or penetrator shells every three seconds. These were supplemented with another four sets of one-inch repeater anti-air cannons installed lower down on the sides of the ship. Two port side and two starboard. The Vengeance was classed as a light cruiser, but under Serena’s command, making use of the… unique aspects of the ship she was able to make it punch well above its weight. To her left and right were the port and starboard observation posts. These small rooms jutted out over the ship's structure and allowed direct observation of the sides o...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Four: The Battle of Port Highwind</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1765360/chapter-four-the-battle-of-port-highwind</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1765360/chapter-four-the-battle-of-port-highwind</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 15:01:15 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“Pitch up! Twenty degrees!” Returning to the bridge, Serena had been greeted by the familiar air of pre-battle tension. There was no changing plans now, no more debating and theory-crafting over maps of defenses. They were locked in, their hand having been dealt and the dice thrown. Port Highwind was an important logistic hub for the Republic, through which demonkind had long suspected aid was funneled in from the other human nations. It was the largest island of the archipelago, floating three klicks above the lumina. Despite its importance, due to its ability to act as a supply hub for the front line, the port only kept a squadron of frigates and interceptors. Even that was somewhat impressive, considering the state of the war. It wasn’t the frigates that were the port’s primary protection, those scouts and light-ships were mostly there to send early warning to the Republic’s reserve fleets, which would scramble from the air-staging bases in the north, thirty klicks out. No, it was t...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Five: The Contract</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1766115/chapter-five-the-contract</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1766115/chapter-five-the-contract</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 23:34:59 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Amelia smiled at her demon captain, feeling the aether inside her begging to be expressed, to be spoken . The pressure was unusual, reminding her of the few times she had flown on an airplane and how her ears would pop. Although, this pressure was across her entire body and felt… nice. “ Divine healing of Aseco. ” Warmth, love, and light exploded from her body, filling the space with waves of gold and blue. Amelia felt the aether pour out of her, and the atmosphere seemed to hum in satisfaction as it was saturated with energy. She could sense the spell seeking out the injured demons, wanting to fix them, to make them whole again. Inside her, Amelia could faintly feel her aether reserves slightly reduce. It was of little concern though, the ridiculous base stats she’d inherited gave her a titanic amount of aether regeneration. The last wisps of golden light dissipated, and silence filled the air. Two crimson eyes, situated under two very pretty horns were wide with shock, looking at her...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Six: Korvus the Mad Dog</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1767857/chapter-six-korvus-the-mad-dog</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1767857/chapter-six-korvus-the-mad-dog</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 09:13:09 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[As they approached the large group of humans huddling together in the square, Amelia felt a knot of anxiety grow in her stomach. It was bizarre. She felt comfortable around demons, yet the idea of being around humans felt strange, almost unnatural. She figured she had inherited all of her powers from her game character, and had verified much of it; Amelia had previously found time to play around with her aether, to fold it upon itself in different ways as she prepared the intention to Speak some of the many Words she knew from the many combat branches she specialized in. It was a pleasant surprise to find they all seemed to be available to her, and most interestingly, they appeared to provoke certain emotions as they were prepared. Perhaps this was why healing made her feel so good . Knowing that, and feeling the anxiety in her stomach, Amelia pondered as to whether she had also inherited the demonic trait of being mistrustful of humans, despite being a literal human herself. Or was sh...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Seven: Confession</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1771401/chapter-seven-confession</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1771401/chapter-seven-confession</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:46:49 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[The Word was Spoken and power, chaos, and violence erupted from Serena. Korvus was blown back, slamming through the wall of a building, collapsing it upon himself. The citadel was destroyed, unable to withstand the force of the Spoken Word. The stone walls crumbled, dooming any demons inside to a horrific death. Those below, humans and demons alike, were thrown back, piling up against the sides of the buildings ringing the far side of the square in a mass of bodies and broken limbs. Their lives were saved only by the distance from the Spoken Word. She hovered there, in the air, her connection with the aetherfield so strong that she could mimic the levitation effect of the lifting engine of the Vengeance , of which she could sense in the distance, the pulses from it beating through the aetherfield like a heart. Something else is there . A thought arrived in her head, formed from curiosity that was not her own. Her attention was pulled to the black ship in the distance. Something strange...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Eight: What’s Chicken?</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1773070/chapter-eight-whats-chicken</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1773070/chapter-eight-whats-chicken</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 22:51:41 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena woke to the familiar ceiling of wood and steel. She was somewhere in the Vengeance . The room was dim, the aetherlights having been turned down to their lowest setting. Was it nighttime? There were no windows to check. She was lying on a bed, not her usual hammock. The medical wing. Why was she here? Was she injured in battle? She couldn’t remember. Serena moved an arm and then cried out as the movement caused her skin to crack and bleed. Her cry of pain further caused her face to fracture. Through the blinding agony came a thought of understanding. Her soul had been damaged. She must have lost control of the Word. Why? When had she Spoken? Serena tried to call for Anathor, but as she did a golden hue filled the room, mending her skin and dulling the pain. It was only a temporary measure, as soon as the warmth faded she could feel it building back up again. A soul damaged by divine possession was not so easily healed. “Sleep now, Captain. If you could…” came Anathor’s voice. And...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Nine: Arcwhale</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1774009/chapter-nine-arcwhale</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1774009/chapter-nine-arcwhale</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 18:26:31 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“Dismissed!” The officers on the bridge returned to their stations. There was a feeling of relief among the soldiers, seeing Serena fully functional and barking orders, as usual, did wonders for their morale. A crew with a captain who was unconscious for an unknown length of time was a tenuous situation, especially post-mutiny. The demons on the bridge chatted amicably amongst themselves, whilst the air and ground tacticians did what they usually did and debated hypothetical scenarios. Although their ground forces had been disbanded by the Dragon, the ground tactician was technically part of the navy and not the army and had thus remained. His acumen of human defensive strategies would be invaluable in planning future missions of all kinds. They were well into Imperial airspace, and their aetherscopes were picking up frequent transport ships of both military and civilian origin. The atmosphere was casual, the pre-battle tensions long gone. Now with days of free time behind and in front...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Ten: The Second and Third Words</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1774745/chapter-ten-the-second-and-third-words</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1774745/chapter-ten-the-second-and-third-words</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 11:31:15 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“One at a time, you bloody demons! You’re like a pack of damn wolfhounds! One at a time!” The rabble slightly calmed down at the head cook’s bellowing, but it took only moments for it to fall back into a frenzy again, encouraged by the exclamations of the demons who managed to get their meal. “Seven hells! How can something taste so good!?” “I must have died! I definitely died!” “I feel like a right proper noble eating this, ha!” “Me next! Me! I was first!” The sardis was being filleted and cooked as quickly as possible. The sound of its sizzling flesh as it was placed on the hot plate was tantalizing. A rich mouth-watering aroma filled the air and contributed to the chaos of impatient hungry demons. “Miss Thornheart! Gut these two!” “Yes, Head Cook!” Amelia hurried to the part of the kitchen that had been designated as the gutting station. She used a sharp knife to make an incision from the sardis’s tail to its gills, being careful not to cut too deep and penetrate the internal organs...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Eleven: Sensei</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1782827/chapter-eleven-sensei</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1782827/chapter-eleven-sensei</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 21:21:51 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Amelia gripped the wooden sword with both hands and stared down her opponent. Serena was turned slightly to the side, her own wooden sword pointed to the floor as she exuded confidence. The wind gently rustled her black hair, contrasting against the evening sky. “First lesson,” she said as she slowly approached Amelia, who gripped the wooden sword even tighter as the threat loomed. “Don’t grip the sword too tightly; you don’t want to tire your hands.” Amelia relaxed her hands a little and the moment she did a flick of Serena’s wrist wrenched the sword from her grasp and flung it to the ground. “Not that loose,” Serena said, a smile forming on her lips. Amelia grabbed the weapon and once again faced the captain as a titter of chuckles sounded from the others. They were on the first deck, and a circle of demons had formed, providing an impromptu arena. After asking Serena why so many of the crew were watching, the captain shrugged and said, ‘Evening entertainment’ ! “Second, let’s fix th...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twelve: Polina Volkova</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1783923/chapter-twelve-polina-volkova</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1783923/chapter-twelve-polina-volkova</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 18:16:35 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“Polina Volkova?” A speckled youth with a baby face and circles around his eyes called out as he opened the door to her office. They didn’t even knock anymore. It was somewhat understandable, as they were swamped with work from sunrise to sunset, and the juniors were running on less sleep than she was. “Yes…” Polina groaned. It was too early to deal with others. Couldn't she have a little quiet time alone first? “What is it?” “Priority from upstairs.” The junior handed her a large sealed envelope. “Right,” She said, gesturing to the pile of documents and envelopes on one side of the desk. “Shall I put it with my backlog of priority assignments here? Or perhaps…” She waved towards the other side of the desk, where another tower of paper lay waiting. “Should it go under the extra-important priority backlog?” The junior shrugged. “It’s more… extra-important - right-now priority,” he gestured for her to look at the document. Polina saw the red stamp pressed upon the envelope and resisted t...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirteen: A Puzzling Nightmare</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1784610/chapter-thirteen-a-puzzling-nightmare</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1784610/chapter-thirteen-a-puzzling-nightmare</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 08:50:06 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena’s thoughts were muddled - like pushing through tar - she tried to figure out why the old stairwell was oddly familiar. She had been here before, but when? It felt like… the Vengeance’s stairwell. However, things were different and not quite right. Where were the steel deck plates? Why were there greasy oil lanterns hanging from the walls instead of the usual aetherlights? “I’m dreaming again,” she muttered, the sound of her voice reaching her ears a half second after she spoke. An unnatural fog clung around her, muffling sounds and preventing the light from reaching too far. Serena unhooked one of the oil lanterns and cast it about, peering through the darkness. The metal hinge on the lantern squeaked as she moved. There it was again. The heavy wood door stood before her. The familiar words etched into it. Fourth Deck . Why was she here again? Serena tried to think and remember. There was something… something about Amelia. She found her hand holding the key. The captain’s key. S...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fourteen: Kenhoro</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1786594/chapter-fourteen-kenhoro</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1786594/chapter-fourteen-kenhoro</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 15:00:58 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[With a hiss of steam and a clunk, the metal gangway came to a stop. A familiar man in a dark blue uniform was waiting for her. A double pair of small horns crowned his head from which an enormous ponytail flowed. From behind a pair of spectacles, sharp green eyes glared at her, a rare trait that suggested the man had ancestry from the far West. “Dockmaster Yu. Always a pleasure to see you well,” Serena said smoothly with a smile. She had come to appreciate Shin Yu, the dockmaster of Kenhoro. “You!” He pointed a finger at her. “Get that ship out of my docks! Go somewhere else! Why come to Kenhoro, huh!?” Shin waved to the east. “The Tanhae docks are over there! Yes, hello!? I can hear them now! They want you to go over there! Shoo! Bye bye!” He motioned with his hands frantically. Shin Yu spoke Imperial with a thick accent, and much of his native Manwese tone slipped through. He was unbelievably direct when speaking Imperial, lacking the full vocabulary to be more tactful. Not that anyo...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifteen: Matching Masks</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1788513/chapter-fifteen-matching-masks</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1788513/chapter-fifteen-matching-masks</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 19:26:25 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[As Serena led her charge towards the center of Kenhoro she was constantly bombarded with questions. Amelia was intrigued by every little sight or smell. Honestly, it was endearing to see somebody so fascinated by demon culture. On more than one occasion, Serena had to stop Amelia from walking into someone as she was so distracted by the next shiny thing. She did her best to answer what she could, although she often failed to give further detail when the inevitable follow-up questions were thrown her way. The culture in Kenhoro and the surrounding area was familiar to her due to her military career, which caused her to spend a significant amount of time docked. However, she was not a native, and her homeland - The Three Sisters - was several hundred klicks to the southeast. “This is the Kenhoro procession, the main thoroughfare in the city,” she said to Amelia as they stepped onto the enormous paved street. Frequent trams passed them, excess steam hissing out the tops as they trundled p...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Sixteen: A Highguard Mystery</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1789424/chapter-sixteen-a-highguard-mystery</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1789424/chapter-sixteen-a-highguard-mystery</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:22:37 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Hotel Highguard oozed wealth. Its lobby was lined with marble walls, and the floor was covered with a shiny black rock Amelia had never seen before. A dozen pedestals were dotted about, each holding an expensive-looking piece of earthware inscribed with ornate patterns. On the far side of the lobby, a grand staircase layered with a red carpet led to the floors above. There were two elevators to one side, each with a demon attendant. “Take your raincoat and hat off,” Serena said as she removed her own. “Hold these,” she said, passing them to Amelia, who tried to fold them awkwardly over her arm while holding the gift-wrapped bag from the market outside. “Hurry up,” Serena commanded as she strutted off to the reception. “Yes, Lady Halen!” Amelia piped up, remembering Serena’s instructions to be on her best behaviour. She followed behind obediently. The receptionist gave a deep bow as they approached. “Welcome to the Highguard, Speaker Halen,” said the receptionist politely, “Or do you pr...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Seventeen: Coffee Before The Storm</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1794395/chapter-seventeen-coffee-before-the-storm</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1794395/chapter-seventeen-coffee-before-the-storm</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 19:43:06 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[As they plummeted down, the wind roared in Serena’s ears and Amelia's grip almost crushed her hand that was covered in second-level aura. Seven hells! The human was strong when she wanted to be! The ground rushed up to meet them and Serena smashed through a wooden table, denting the stone floor underneath and throwing up dust and splinters. To her right, Amelia had somehow gone through the table head first, face-planting the stone floor. Her legs wiggled in the air and she was making weird whimpering noises. Serena removed her hand from Amelia’s crushing grip and pulled the struggling human upwards by her ankle. “That was amazing!” An upside-down Amelia exclaimed when her face appeared. “Can we do it again!? Oh my, the adrenaline rush! I feel wonderful!” Serena rolled her eyes and opened her hand, letting Amelia fall into a crumpled heap. At least the idiot was okay. “Old man?” She called out, turning to see Lord Yulan clamber smoothly out of a bed of soil and plants. She wasn’t sure h...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Eighteen: Mutual Confession</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1796024/chapter-eighteen-mutual-confession</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1796024/chapter-eighteen-mutual-confession</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 21:55:14 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena was thrown back, smashing through the wall into the building beyond. Despite being wrapped in yellow-aura the shock caused her to bite through her tongue. She spat blood, raising an arm to protect herself as the ceiling collapsed on her. She hurried the Word to form, layering the aether upon itself, folding it into the required structure for communion with Narean . Surprisingly, she found it formed with surprising obedience . Speaking Narean always included a brief battle of will, a demonstration that the Speaker still possessed the power and determination to demand the abilities of the demonic sword god. This time, Narean seemed almost eager to assist. Was this because she was so much stronger after crossing the boundary into blue-aura? Or did Amelia’s ward help in some way? Despite the aether going wild outside, and the wood and stone forming into sharp points that tried to piece her through, Serena was resolute. She wouldn’t allow the skills of Salinas, the Earthlord, to cut ...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Nineteen: The Greatlord of Kenhoro</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1797002/chapter-nineteen-the-greatlord-of-kenhoro</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1797002/chapter-nineteen-the-greatlord-of-kenhoro</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:41:37 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Amelia gripped the handhold Serena had created and pulled herself up before seeking the next one. Serena was just in front, using her magic to create little holes in the earth and stone. Together they ascended up the hole the Salinas Speaker had desperately created to escape. Amelia could have jumped out easily, or used earth magic herself to bring the both of them to the surface. Instead, she was glad they had silently agreed to this slow ascent. It gave each of them valuable time to think and Amelia had plenty to think about. Her mind raced between the sheer embarrassment of breaking down and crying in front of Serena, and the celebratory feeling of delight and satisfaction she felt over the most amazing kiss anyone had ever experienced! Best of all, Serena had initiated! Nothing else could have assured Amelia her feelings were reciprocated as much as Serena’s hand wrapping around her head and pulling her in so gently and so boldly! As she adjusted her limbs into the next set of hand...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty: Two Girlfriends And Many Drinks</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1798241/chapter-twenty-two-girlfriends-and-many-drinks</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1798241/chapter-twenty-two-girlfriends-and-many-drinks</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 13:56:36 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[The door swung shut behind them - leaving them in silence - staring at the bed whose very existence made Amelia’s heart race. Amelia cast an eye sideways to see Serena with a nervous expression on her face. The demon was chewing her lips. “Well!” Amelia exclaimed as cheerfully as she could. “It looks very… cosy, doesn’t it?” “I will return to reception. Have them bring another bed,” said Serena, turning to the door. Amelia intercepted her, throwing her arms wide and blocking her passage. “You can’t!” Amelia cried, “We’ve already imposed so much on Mister Weng! We can’t bother him any more!” “We’re paying customers; it’s his job to be bothered.” Serena crossed her arms and tried to look stern, although her flushed cheeks somewhat spoiled the act. “It’s the last room, Mister Weng must be very busy running a full establishment! We can bother him tomorrow!” Amelia wasn’t going to let this gift from the gods go unused. This was something to fight over! “Don’t be silly. We’re Speakers . It’s...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-One: The Kenhoro Officer Academy</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1799666/chapter-twenty-one-the-kenhoro-officer-academy</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1799666/chapter-twenty-one-the-kenhoro-officer-academy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 09:08:30 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“You’re here,” grumbled the grizzled captain as Serena once again found herself standing in an ethereal fog that stretched endlessly into the darkness. “You’ve committed a cardinal sin,” the captain said, his voice muffled in the unnatural expanse. “There will be a punishment.” Serena’s thoughts were full of Amelia, and she felt anger rise within her. Was she still drunk? She was probably still drunk. “For falling for a woman? A human?” She snapped at the illusive man, who didn’t react at all to her outburst. “Too late… you must protect the girl…” the captain grumbled, removing his captain’s hat to reveal messy grey hair and the edges of an aged face. Serena paused, realising this dream figure was human . “I’m heading to the ice-lands to do my part. As for you…” The human battered the side of his hat, knocking dirt and dust loose. The rhythmic beating of his palm against the brown leather sent shockwaves throughout the space. “... the pair of you must go to the desert. The old temple…”...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-Two: Grandmaster Grandpa</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1811576/chapter-twenty-two-grandmaster-grandpa</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1811576/chapter-twenty-two-grandmaster-grandpa</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 11:48:43 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“How’d this happen, then?” Serena asked Amelia, lightly kicking the stone encasing the complaining demon. “This weirdo ,” Amelia made sure to emphasise that word for extra effect, “Came up to me like some homeless beggar and tried to get me to go with him to some traveller’s bed or whatever! Shameless!” “Is that so?” Serena intoned, drawing her marbled sword, “Which bit do you want me to cut off first, Aiden the Drunk? ” The blade glowed red as aura coursed through it, causing the trapped demon’s eyes to shake in panic. There was an older demon with Serena who was watching the events with an amused expression on his face. He looked old and gave her a grandfather vibe, but Amelia’s instincts told her he was on par if not more dangerous than Serena was. A Speaker of at least one Word, for sure. “T-traveller’s Rest!” The trapped demon cried, “Traveller’s Rest! It’s a new pale ale from the Sabanis Dominance! I thought we could get a drink while we waited for you to do whatever you were doi...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-Three: Tea With The Empress</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1811577/chapter-twenty-three-tea-with-the-empress</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1811577/chapter-twenty-three-tea-with-the-empress</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 11:48:51 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Amelia blocked the three-strike combination with ease. Now that she knew how to tense the muscles in the right places to avoid her guard collapsing, defending against the attacks that came in a half-second was becoming satisfyingly easy. Another dozen swings came at her from the grandmaster. At first, it was a challenge, but then Amelia understood it was only a matter of figuring out how to move her body in a way that could keep up with her perception. She could see every attack and follow the sword's path through the air. Seeing, however, was very different from being able to do something about it. A swing from an unfamiliar direction came at the end of the combination, and the strike broke through her improvised deflection before stopping at the centre of her chest. “That was mune-tsuki , the chest thrust,” The grandmaster grumbled. “Here, this is how you deflect it.” Amelia was shown in ever-increasing detail how to defend against a thrust. She gave her utmost attention, not wanting...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-Four: Breaking Boundaries</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1813255/chapter-twenty-four-breaking-boundaries</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1813255/chapter-twenty-four-breaking-boundaries</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2024 11:32:41 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[The week building up to the festival was a blur of activities, new experiences and satisfying bedtime exercises that were slowly becoming increasingly risque. As they became more comfortable with each other's bodies, Amelia felt their connection grow. When they were alone, she would sometimes sit on Serena's lap, interrupting her work. While the demon would click her tongue and roll her eyes, Serena would still embrace and kiss her before complaining about being distracted from her paperwork. They kept up the appearance with the futon but otherwise cuddled each other to sleep. Serena seemed to like it when Amelia buried her head into her chest, so that became their typical sleeping position. They would talk about each other's lives and hold as little back as possible. Serena couldn’t share everything as she was a commissioned officer, and so some things needed to remain secret. “I suppose there’s one thing I’ve been wondering…” Serena mumbled one night while Amelia was nestled into her...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-Five: Breaking Bones</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1814749/chapter-twenty-five-breaking-bones</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1814749/chapter-twenty-five-breaking-bones</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 15:08:36 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[After an awkward exchange of morning greetings, Serena took a shower in the washroom. She sat down as the warm water rained down upon her, clutching both her horns in a mixture of embarrassment and frustration. Was it normal for her thoughts and emotions to be so strong ? She knew she liked Amelia, but the magnitude of her urges and how often she gave into them was like nothing she had ever experienced before. What she did to Amelia last night - what she enjoyed doing - were things she never thought she would ever do to another person, let alone a human . She’d lost herself in raw desire, and that smug idiot - her girlfriend - had only encouraged her! Was everyone else this passionate behind closed doors? Or was their relationship different? The romance she had toyed with during her academy years was nothing like this. She let out a soft groan. Infatuation. That was the word that described her situation. Every time she had let her attraction to Amelia manifest into action, the human wa...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-Six: The Moonrain Festival</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1816757/chapter-twenty-six-the-moonrain-festival</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1816757/chapter-twenty-six-the-moonrain-festival</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:06:30 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[After having her hair ruffled and cheeks squeezed, Amelia was able to recount the tale of events to an annoyed-looking Serena. Her girlfriend’s glare softened when Amelia explained Grandmaster Gu’s reaction and the hair ruffling slowly changed into a gentle head massage. “Mmm…” Amelia murmured, “I don’t understand why they got so aggressive so fast. I would have thought trainee officers would be far more composed…” “Idiot,” Serena replied, running her hands through Amelia’s golden hair. She sat Amelia down and began to comb through the ruffled mess. “Some of it was probably anti-human bias. They’re trainee officers; you know the first thing that gets drilled into your head throughout your time at the academy?” “What?” “To watch out for human spies. That’s the singular lesson that gets repeated constantly throughout the years. Then you turn up in their academy, poking your nose in their training. If you were a spy, think about the information you could get,” Serena explained, slowly tea...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-Seven: A Good Show</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1817757/chapter-twenty-seven-a-good-show</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1817757/chapter-twenty-seven-a-good-show</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 12:34:10 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[When Serena turned and showed Amelia her painted peeka face it was only the result of a titanic amount of self-control and the presence of Aiden that prevented her from blurting out something entirely inappropriate. While she bit her tongue to stop giggling with enough force to crush a warrior wrapped in orange aura, Amelia was delighted to see that Serena seemed to be facing the same predicament. “Look at you two,” Aiden said, as the finishing touches were made to his painted shawa face, “I’m king of the forest! You can be members of my pack! Here,” Aiden offered them another beer from his bag, “You can share some of my kill!” “King of the drunks, more like,” Serena said, turning her mirth-filled gaze from Amelia’s face and towards Aiden before snatching the bottle. “Do shawas and peekas hunt in packs?” Amelia asked, not quite able to imagine the lion-like shawa with a pack of peekas . The latter seemed even more friendly than the domesticated housecats from her world. “No, they’ll ge...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-Eight: The Merchant Girl From Tanhae</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1819467/chapter-twenty-eight-the-merchant-girl-from-tanhae</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1819467/chapter-twenty-eight-the-merchant-girl-from-tanhae</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 12:32:13 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“And how did all this happen?” Aiden asked as he stepped into the room carrying a tray of food. The restaurant workers he was assisting let out little gasps of shock as they took in the scene of devastation and lust-driven violence. “ She happened,” Amelia said with a grin, gesturing to Serena standing proudly over a pile of unconscious demons. “The one with three pairs of horns put his blade against my throat so Speaker Halen protected me,” Amelia emphasised Serena’s title as a Speaker, which had the intended effect; the restaurant employees suddenly became very docile, and their eyes took on a mixture of fear and respect as they fixed their gaze upon Serena. She figured that considering Serena’s status as a lord-prospect, war hero, and Speaker, the establishment might be willing to avoid the hassle of kicking them out. Her prediction turned out to be correct as the owner soon appeared and after a quiet conversation with Serena and Aiden the unconscious rabble was taken away. They eve...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Twenty-Nine: Polina’s Confusion</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1822822/chapter-twenty-nine-polinas-confusion</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1822822/chapter-twenty-nine-polinas-confusion</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:48:52 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Mel paced in front of the door to the training room. Back and forth she went, too distracted in her thoughts to stop. Her throat was constricted and she felt like she wanted to be sick. A pit of anxiety had formed in her stomach that gnawed at her mental state. She wanted desperately just to run away. Unfortunately, running away was tricky while her broken arm was wrapped in a sling. For the third time, she raised her fist to knock and for the third time, she hesitated. Beyond that door were not one, not two, but three Speakers! How was she supposed to be able to handle that! “You can do it, you can do it…” she muttered to herself like a mantra. She squeezed every bit of mental strength she could muster and knocked on the door. There was no answer. Of course there was no answer. This training room was a private area for instructors and Speakers. She knew about the famous sound-blocking enhancements covering its thick wooden walls. She reached down and before her instincts could stop he...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty: The Second Word of Divinity</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1826445/chapter-thirty-the-second-word-of-divinity</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1826445/chapter-thirty-the-second-word-of-divinity</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 17:12:53 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[For the next week and a half Amelia followed a simple schedule. First, she would wake up in Serena’s arms and give her a blast of healing magic. Serena had remarked that she suspected her body might be getting younger as a side-effect, although she wasn’t sure. The pair of them decided to keep an eye on things. The next daily task was washing, followed by breakfast and a morning coffee. Serena had raised an eyebrow when Amelia returned with a twenty-pound sack of Jimari coffee beans but otherwise didn’t say anything. Tomes continued to turn up in the morning and help teach Amelia writing and reading. She was getting good now and could understand more and more complex sentences. She also enjoyed the mathematics books he had brought her and was delighted to find that demons had discovered calculus! Although they used different symbols that felt strange at first, she got used to them. On seeing how proficient she was with numbers, Serena mentioned that her oldest sister, Nina, would get a...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-One: Observation</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1827447/chapter-thirty-one-observation</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1827447/chapter-thirty-one-observation</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 09:55:37 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Faren gripped the ship's railing with white knuckles, forcing himself to take deep breaths as the upper-sky island came into view. Of all his friends and acquaintances, he didn’t know anyone who got more air sick than he did. He felt queasy travelling on a tiny ship like this, especially as the storm season winds meant he was constantly off balance. “Ready with the rope, Mister Faren!” yelled the captain, struggling to keep the ship’s wheel from spinning out of control. “Look! They’re waiting!” the captain gestured with his chin at the approaching island, and Faren squinted to see a pair of demons waving from a small jetty. Faren braced himself as the ship came ever closer, holding the hefty rope in one hand while trying to keep himself steady with the other. The winds battered the ship, tilting it this way and that. He groaned silently to himself. He’d been assured his career in sensors and communications would mean a dull but stable life in an office somewhere. Unfortunately, things ...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-Two: Who Is Amelia Thornheart?</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1827448/chapter-thirty-two-who-is-amelia-thornheart</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1827448/chapter-thirty-two-who-is-amelia-thornheart</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 09:56:05 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[In one moment, Serena saw Amelia’s eyes filled with fear, hope, and determination. Then Amelia Spoke, and night became day. The aetherfield twisted and boiled as energies manifested at levels she had never seen or experienced before. These forces didn’t harm her; they simply flowed about, announcing to the world, ‘ I am here! ’. Then the night returned, and Amelia was gone. In her place, a pair of gigantic taloned feet gripped the ship, each one large enough to wrap around Serena’s body. She gulped and turned her head upwards to see that much of the night sky was covered by a pair of enormous black feather wings. Each stretched for more than a hundred feet, and the dark feathers twinkled with hints of colour, reminding Serena of the sky during moonrains, where the crystals burned up in the atmosphere in bright flashes. Much of Amelia’s elongated form was now covered in the same dark feathers. They covered her shoulders, chest, and arms in layered patterns that reminded Serena of scale ...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-Three: Interrogation I</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1830341/chapter-thirty-three-interrogation-i</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1830341/chapter-thirty-three-interrogation-i</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 20:13:28 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[With every step, Amelia felt herself bond closer to her divine form. She walked on her six limbs, as the movement felt more natural given her elongated body. Her talons were razor sharp and easily sliced through earth, stone, and wood. Her great wings were difficult to control entirely, but depending on her will, they could become an impenetrable shield or wall of soft feathers. The endless ocean of aether inside her begged to be used, circulating throughout her body and pushing her senses to new heights. It wasn’t just the feeling of her vast reserves; Amelia could feel her body drawing in the aetherfield. It was like she was a vacuum, and the ethereal substance was rushing to fill her up. At the same time, she was continuously expelling aether back into the atmosphere, creating a continuous process that she could only describe as breathing aether. Her perception had grown tremendously, and her ability to process information had similarly caught up. Before, she could sense the aether ...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-Four: Interrogation II</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1830648/chapter-thirty-four-interrogation-ii</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1830648/chapter-thirty-four-interrogation-ii</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 01:45:59 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“W-w-wh-” Polina stuttered, her face drained of colour and eyes wide in fear. “Wh- what’s that!” She had scrambled backwards, pressing her body hard against the tree. “Har har!” Amelia bounced around the area, clambering up a tree and looking down on the shaking Polina. “It’s me! Amelia! Aren’t I cute!” Amelia dropped down and approached the pair. Serena was groaning and rubbing her forehead. Concerned that perhaps she was getting a headache, Amelia fired off another round of healing and cleaning. Polina’s blessing had activated when Amelia had announced her identity. Interestingly, it seemed to pass through her defences as if her wards weren’t even there. There was no blessing mechanic in the game she had played in the hospital. They seemed to work under entirely different principles compared to regular aether magic. Still, if Polina’s blessing did let her know that Amelia was telling the truth; that she was especially amazing and adorable in this form, then things would progress easi...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-Five: Little Big Horns</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1832753/chapter-thirty-five-little-big-horns</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1832753/chapter-thirty-five-little-big-horns</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 12:31:35 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Wings! She did have wings! Amelia couldn’t contain her growing excitement and leapt up, bouncing around the area, giggling uncontrollably. “You mean it!?” she asked Serena as she stopped and began tippy-tapping the floor with her four hands. “We’re going to fly to Shimashina!? You’re going to ride me!?” “Ha!” Serena exclaimed, looking amused at Amelia’s antics. “Not quite. We’ll fly within fifty klicks of the city and enter the forest before the perimeter ships and their aetherscopes can pick you up. Then you’ll transform back, and we'll run the final leg. We-” Serena frowned. “Hang on.” She vanished into the ship, where Amelia could sense her collecting their luggage. While that was happening, a small voice piped up. “We’re really going to… fly?” Polina asked in a small voice. Amelia flashed a gigantic smile. “Looks like it! Don’t worry, I’ll ward you so if anything goes wrong you’ll be unharmed!” At her words, Polina’s eyes widened and a small smile appeared on her face. “Ward me? Of...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-Six: Father and Daughter</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1834461/chapter-thirty-six-father-and-daughter</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1834461/chapter-thirty-six-father-and-daughter</guid><pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 14:54:49 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“We’re almost there,” Serena said as the carriage trundled along the road. There were no tramlines to the outskirts of Shimashina, so they had to make do with a horse-drawn carriage. “Remember your lessons. First impressions are important, especially towards my father.” The father in question would undoubtedly meet them when they arrived. Hopefully, their lateness didn't irritate him. After she and Amelia had run the last fifty klicks to Shimashina, rode the plateau lifts, met with the Vengeance's officers and explained what had happened, the sky had already darkened. “Don’t worry! I’m sure he’ll like me!” Amelia flashed a thumbs up, her now-crimson eyes brimming with excitement. From what Serena knew, it was normal for a Second Word transformation to leave lingering physical effects. Amelia was quite lucky only her eyes had changed since transforming back. Only time would tell whether they would stay red or eventually revert to her usual blue. “Just… try only to speak when spoken to. ...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-Seven: A Whispered Confession</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1837937/chapter-thirty-seven-a-whispered-confession</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1837937/chapter-thirty-seven-a-whispered-confession</guid><pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 21:04:45 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena sat down at the ironwood table. It wasn’t comparable to the enormous gold-trimmed table in the grand dining hall at their home estate. Instead, this table only politely whispered of House Halen’s wealth. The rest of the room continued in a similar vein, boasting great tapestries and heavily-framed paintings. While not produced by the most skilled artists in the Empire, these still exuded a quiet sense of affluence. Looking across the table, Serena found the Empress of Cascadia looking back at her. At least, through painted eyes. “What made you choose that incarnation?” she asked Father, nodding towards the painting. “The horns,” he replied, sitting next to her. “Your grandfather had horns that curved back like that, a sign of his southern heritage. Also, her black hair reminds me of my beautiful daughters, even when they cause me endless trouble.” Serena eyed the painting. The dignified and stoic depiction of the Divine Empress consciously made her straighten her posture and rai...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-Eight: Chesterfield</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1845774/chapter-thirty-eight-chesterfield</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1845774/chapter-thirty-eight-chesterfield</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 19:31:50 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Amelia blinked awake in the embrace of Serena’s arms. She was warm, cosy, and wanted to do nothing but lie here for hours listening to her girlfriend’s cute snoring. Serena, of course, denied snoring adamantly . Her snoring had become yet another tool in Amelia’s ever-growing repertoire of things to tease Serena about. Amelia stared at the creeping morning light bathing the room for a few minutes until the sound of footsteps reached her ears. They were too energetic to be a servant and too light to be Dalinar’s, Serena’s father. There was only one person they could be. Lani! As the footsteps made their way down the hallway, Amelia elbowed Serena awake. “Lani’s outside,” she whispered, prompting Serena to sit up frantically. Despite the situation, Amelia couldn’t help appreciating Serena’s bed hair and how the light bounced off her horns. A knock sounded, not at the door to Serena’s room, but at the door to Amelia’s room opposite. “Amelia! Let’s have breakfast!” Lani said cheerfully. Wh...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Thirty-Nine: Shadow and Splinters</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1853078/chapter-thirty-nine-shadow-and-splinters</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1853078/chapter-thirty-nine-shadow-and-splinters</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:24:15 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena vaguely sensed a disruption in the aetherfield before the skull's eyes glowed red, and a familiar gruff voice spoke out. “Hmm… Captain. Miss Thornheart,” Anathor intoned in greeting. Serena opened her mouth as a question formed but quickly closed it. Anathor had once told her he could leave the ship if he had to, but it wasn’t a good idea as the ship would begin to behave strangely if he was gone for too long. As captain of the Vengeance, Serena had never known Anathor to leave. At least, not to her knowledge. “No greeting for me, Anathor?” Chesterfield said with a soft smile. “Hmm… hello, Chesterfield,” the skull eventually mumbled after a long silence. “Before we begin,” Chesterfield announced, spreading his hands wide. “I hope you don’t mind, but it’s important that we record this conversation, so…” the demon reached into a pocket and brought out an ornately-cut moon crystal sitting in a small box. Unlike the other box on the table, which gave her an ominous feeling, this one...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty: Priorities</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1860112/chapter-forty-priorities</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1860112/chapter-forty-priorities</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 19:27:03 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“That’s impossible,” Serena said again, knowing her words contradicted the ominous reality before her. Her heartbeat shot up and adrenaline filled her body, causing her to shake. The black moon crystal made her grit her teeth in anxiety. Strangely, the sight of it also prompted a deep feeling of anger . It was as if the existence of this crystal was an offence to all living things. She hated this crystal, and somehow, she knew it hated her. “Weird…” Amelia muttered, shuddering and rubbing her arms. “Hmm… never gets easier…” Anathor mumbled. The ethereal shadow spreading from the crystal could not reach the glowing skull. Whatever abilities Anathor possessed, it was enough to prevent the corruption from getting too close. “Here,” Chesterfield said, reaching over and picking up the crystal with only the slightest bit of hesitation. “It’s uncomfortable but not painful,” he explained, holding it out to her. Shadow spewed from the crystal and covered his hand, frothing over and falling towa...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-One: A Nighttime Chat</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1868268/chapter-forty-one-a-nighttime-chat</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1868268/chapter-forty-one-a-nighttime-chat</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:57:23 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Lani was bored. Father had instructed her to stay out of the way while he had important guests, but that was hours ago. What was she supposed to do? Sit in her room and poke holes in her pillow with her horns? Annoyingly, that was precisely what she had been doing! After thoroughly destroying one pillow, Lani sat up in bed and proceeded to tilt her head back, leaving two small dents in the wooden frame behind her. “I… Am… Bored…” Lani muttered, punctuating each word by nodding backwards and further damaging the wooden bedframe. On the bright side, her horns had grown enough to do this! A year ago, she’d had to bend her neck all the way back! “Lani, my dear,” said the old maid sitting across the room. “How much of the house are you intending to destroy with your horns?” The old maid spoke in that you're-being-childish - and-we-both-know-it tone that annoyed Lani so much. “All of it!” Lani declared, bashing her horns against the wood once again. “Maybe then Father wouldn’t lock me up wit...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-Two: The Cascadian Ambassador</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1872637/chapter-forty-two-the-cascadian-ambassador</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1872637/chapter-forty-two-the-cascadian-ambassador</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 17:58:53 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Anton peered through the windows, watching the arriving ship come into dock above the Numengrad skyline. The capital of the Federation was usually cool this time of year, however, the warm air from the southern storms had finally reached the city, causing an abnormal amount of humidity. Anton opened the window the few inches it allowed. Windows in the Red Citadel - the center of government for the Federation - couldn’t be opened fully. Still, the subtle breeze freshened the room and took away some of the stickiness. The ship docked in the Red Citadel's private airdock where a small group disembarked. Even from this distance, the singular demon in the group was easily identified. Standing a head above the rest, the height difference was further emphasised by two sets of horns. The demon glanced at the Red Citadel with an indecipherable expression before following a guard out of sight. Calvin Cornelissen, the Cascadian Ambassador to the Federation, had arrived. Sighing, Anton walked away...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-Three: Full Broadside</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1882797/chapter-forty-three-full-broadside</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1882797/chapter-forty-three-full-broadside</guid><pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 15:08:23 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“Right then, this looks good enough.” Serena held up her hand, feeling the strength and direction of the wind. Her gunners would need to adjust slightly, but for a crew as experienced as hers, they would hit the target easily enough. “Are you sure this is a real training method?” The target in question complained before putting her hands on her hips and pouting. “You’re not making this up so you can shoot your adorable girlfriend, are you?” Serena felt a sly smile form but otherwise chose not to reply immediately. They’d set sail from Shimashina that morning. After clearing the aetherscope range of the city’s perimeter ships, Serena ordered the Vengeance a few dozen klicks away from the regular travel route and found a small mid-sky island floating six klicks above the continent. Dagon had taken command as acting captain while Serena and Amelia jumped the few dozen meters down onto the island with their training equipment. With only a few thousand square feet and a handful of trees, th...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-Four: Human Mince</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1890062/chapter-forty-four-human-mince</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1890062/chapter-forty-four-human-mince</guid><pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 12:36:08 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[The next day, with only a few hours until they landed at Asamaywa, Amelia was dragged away from her game of Drunk Demon’s Hand where she’d won a significant chunk of Dagon’s monthly pay and was led by Serena out and onto the deck of the Vengeance . “Wow!” Amelia exclaimed, stepping out into the open air and pointing towards the front of the ship. “You can see the airflow!” Like the aircraft from her world, the Vengeance had flaperons. The large panels that extended off the port and starboard side of the ship's hull could be adjusted from the bridge to affect the ship’s roll and help generate lift. An opaque air stream erupted from their tips, trailing the ship's length. “It’s called trailing vortices,” Serena explained. “Happens due to differences in pressure along the flaperon. Atmospheric conditions around the Nai inlet and its mountains are ripe for it when we’re at full sail.” She gestured, and Amelia saw the enormous port and starboard sails fully deployed and catching the westerl...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-Five: The Public's Personage</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1897424/chapter-forty-five-the-publics-personage</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1897424/chapter-forty-five-the-publics-personage</guid><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 15:26:08 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena hadn’t been wrong. The moment Amelia crossed the gangway and set foot on the Asamaywa Imperial Airdocks, several dozen workers ceased their activities and stared at her, stopping only to elbow their coworkers and nod in her direction. Unlike her arrival in Kenhoro, Amelia wasn’t wearing a hat and so her blond hair was as noticeable as a lighthouse aetherlight. Serena suggested Amelia travel covertly throughout the city, but she’d rejected the idea; she was now a Lord-Prospect, and if she wanted to integrate fully into demon society, then the sight of her was something they would need to get used to! Team leaders barked at the distracted workers who scrambled to resume their duties. Still, other demons kept their attention on her; small groups of people dressed in naval officer uniforms mumbled amongst themselves, throwing the occasional glance. Doing her best to ignore them, Amelia chose to look up and down the airdocks, marvelling at how different it was from Kenhoro. The airdo...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-Six: Greatlord Oshiro</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1905633/chapter-forty-six-greatlord-oshiro</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1905633/chapter-forty-six-greatlord-oshiro</guid><pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:49:21 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Greatlord Oshiro shifted slightly in his chair. It wasn’t that his seat was uncomfortable, the atmosphere awkward, or the temperature too hot or cold. No, it was his instincts as a warrior, honed to a standard worthy of his station through thousands of hours of religious practice, that caused him to adjust his weight. It wasn’t a conscious reaction, and he found his body preparing for combat before he identified any obvious threats. The sensation lingered in his mind; the subtle screaming of his instincts informed him of one clear fact unnoticed by everyone else around him. Danger. But from where? It wasn’t from Highlady Halen, the pinnacle of Eastern nobility and Lady of the House Halen, who was chatting amicably while delicately sipping tea. Nor was it from the unparalleled beauty in discussion with her: his wife, Ashina Oshiro. Neither was the threat from the legion of skilled maids that served them with practised grace and elegance. Not even the houseguards, some talented enough to...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-Seven: The Assistant Instructor's Assistant</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1913619/chapter-forty-seven-the-assistant-instructors</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1913619/chapter-forty-seven-the-assistant-instructors</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 01:13:14 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[The carriage trundled away from Serena’s home and towards the academy. Inside, the pitter-patter of steadily increasing raindrops filled the carriage’s cabin. Serena sat, doing her best not to break out into a giggle. Amelia sat opposite her and judging by how she looked everywhere but at Serena, she wasn’t able to make eye contact. “That was… something ,” Serena said before biting her tongue to stop herself from laughing. With a mighty effort, she managed to squeeze out the question, “Did you… enjoy the dinner?” “Uhhh…” came the agonised groan. Amelia didn’t meet Serena’s gaze. Instead, she turned her head slowly and let her body tilt until her forehead smashed against the carriage wall. “I think,” she mumbled. “I think I want to die.” “Nonsense!” Serena replied cheerfully. “It was a wonderful introduction to my Mother and Greatlord Oshiro! You made…” she intentionally paused for dramatic effect, “...a memorable impression.” “Uuhhhh!” Amelia whimpered, her eyes squeezed closed. “You’r...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-Eight: The Northern Swordmaster</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1922097/chapter-forty-eight-the-northern-swordmaster</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1922097/chapter-forty-eight-the-northern-swordmaster</guid><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 20:05:50 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[For the first time in a long time, Serena woke up in an Amelia-less room. Her sleep had undoubtedly suffered for it. She’d become accustomed to the soft warmth of Amelia’s body next to hers, and without her girlfriend’s gentle breathing, the night seemed awfully quiet. She’d tossed and turned for an hour before arranging no less than three pillows into a line next to her, which she held until she eventually fell asleep. The pillows were a poor substitution for her human but they had saved her from a sleepless night. She even found she missed Amelia’s snoring. Amelia refused to admit that someone ‘as cute as she was’ would snore, no matter how often Serena complained about it. It had gotten to the point where Serena was prepared to bring in an axiom crystal to record her as evidence. It was early, and only the very first tendrils of the morning light were streaking through the windows. Before she’d manifested the first aura, mornings like these would be a sordid affair as the chill in t...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Forty-Nine: Aether Addict</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1929485/chapter-forty-nine-aether-addict</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1929485/chapter-forty-nine-aether-addict</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 23:55:23 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[After grumbling and complaining about their tardiness, Grandmaster Shun spent no less than half an hour drilling the pair of them about how they should conduct themselves around the students. Well, it seemed he was drilling the pair of them, but Amelia felt she was the target of most of his instructions and warnings. From what Amelia could decipher, any trouble they caused would reflect badly onto him. As the head of a famous academy Empire-wide, where Cascadian nobility and other wealthy patrons sent their sons and daughters to receive the very pinnacle of military education, there were enormous expectations and pressures placed upon the staff to fulfill their roles flawlessly. Both of them had additional warnings laid out. Most instructors were Speakers, and being Speakers, they not only represented the academy but also the class of society that was looked upon as being divinely chosen. The existence of a Speaker meant they measured up to the expectations of a god , and it wouldn’t d...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty: Duel</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1934282/chapter-fifty-duel</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1934282/chapter-fifty-duel</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 19:15:55 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[With the sensation of her entire body taking an exhilarating cold breath, divine aether flowed in and through Amelia’s body. Power . Since Lunaria had been so kind as to blast Amelia away with her invocation of Igni , Amelia thought it was fair that she returned the favour. She didn’t quite know exactly how strong the surrounding Writing-enforced walls were. Still, her intuition told her that if she maximised the amount of atmospheric aether to be expelled by the incoming god-given aether, the resulting explosion would cause the newly formed House Thornheart to be given a devastatingly expensive repair bill. So she made sure to cycle the aether and expel it beforehand. Well, most of it. She left a fraction in as a tentative test of her aether capacity and to repay Lunaria’s bold opening move. Hopefully, with even such a small amount of her monstrous aether reserves, the effect would still be magnificent. Amelia wasn’t disappointed. The explosion of aether-infused lightning flooded the ...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-One: Firemint Tea</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1943967/chapter-fifty-one-firemint-tea</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1943967/chapter-fifty-one-firemint-tea</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 21:13:00 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[In the academy’s central throughway, Amelia found herself lost in thought as she idly perused the display cabinets lining the walls. Contained within were martial weapons of all types, to which Amelia paid little attention. Her mind was occupied with recent events, and the passing student gossip barely registered. She was filled with a mixture of excitement and doubt. One of the students, a second circle mage named Hinako, enthusiastically requested Amelia’s tutorage. The request was delivered with such solemn determination that Amelia was once again reminded that the magical capabilities she took for granted were of life-changing importance for many of the academy’s students. Amelia had agreed, caught up in the excitement of the prospect of developing her own group of disciples. That wasn’t anything unusual; the teaching documents she’d gone over made it clear that instructors could - and were encouraged to - take on students as direct disciples if it wouldn’t interfere with their oth...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-Two: Crystalcraft</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1951202/chapter-fifty-two-crystalcraft</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1951202/chapter-fifty-two-crystalcraft</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 14:15:13 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Amelia walked as quickly as she could without embarrassing herself. She would only be a few minutes late. Her chat with Sarafina Nakajima had occupied too much time! Sarafina’s company was pleasant and Amelia made a mental note to acquire her own batch of firemint tea leaves. It would compliment her jimari coffee beans quite nicely. Although now wasn’t the time to be thinking about tea. Amelia entered the magic tower and hurried up its spiralling staircase. About halfway up, she double-checked the brass plaque that indicated the floor and stepped off. The magic tower’s rooms were arranged in a circle on each floor, with their doors facing the center. A balcony ringed each floor and provided the only walking space. The academy had installed nets on each floor, stretching from the balcony edge to the stairway, saving any student unlucky enough to fall. “Workshop D…” she muttered, circling the floor and quickly finding the target door. Taking a deep breath and mentally hoping that not eve...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-Three: Red Aura</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1959109/chapter-fifty-three-red-aura</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1959109/chapter-fifty-three-red-aura</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 13:23:55 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena woke at first light. She didn’t open her eyes just yet, instead choosing to enjoy the warm pressure of Amelia leaning into her. It was unbelievable how difficult it was to maintain composure around her. At first, she accepted it as the result of a fledgling infatuation, but in many ways, it only got worse. Was this what it felt like to be madly in love? As the days and weeks ticked by, Serena not only began factoring Amelia into more and more decisions, but she’d also begun working on the assumption they would always be together. An assumption that made Serena giddy. She wrapped an arm around Amelia’s sleeping figure and gave her a small squeeze. Her action earned her a satisfying squeak and something mumbled about fried chicken. Serena slipped out from under the blanket and stood up, quietly yawning as she regulated her aura to resist the morning chill. She glanced through the window and was greeted by a frosty, foggy morning. Turning away, she- Wait, what was that? Serena snap...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-Four: Aftermath</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1968422/chapter-fifty-four-aftermath</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1968422/chapter-fifty-four-aftermath</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 21:23:33 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[“This must never get out,” Grandmaster Shun said, glaring at the three of them. The grandmaster sat at his desk, hands clenched with white knuckles hinting at his controlled anger. Serena, Amelia, and Katalin stood to attention. The demon's presence wasn’t quite as intimidating as the Dragon’s, but it was enough that Serena felt a tinge of nervousness; a part of her instincts raised alarm bells at the sheer violence he was capable of. After Amelia had quite literally disarmed and then rearmed Katalin, they soon moved into the second half of the session. Only Serena, Amelia and the three Head Instructors, Ryosuke, Nathaniel, and Joey, remained while everyone else, exhausted and gossiping over the events that had just transpired, left the room. Katalin seemed especially eager to have Amelia begin sparring with her newly formed red aura. And what an aura it was! Serena didn’t think she’d ever seen a red aura with such vibrant hues. Looking at Amelia’s aura was fascinating; it somehow seem...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-Five: The Shimmer and The Formless</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1979535/chapter-fifty-five-the-shimmer-and-the-formless</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1979535/chapter-fifty-five-the-shimmer-and-the-formless</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 19:25:46 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Amelia quietly observed the first-year class. It was led by Instructor Kawas, who, aided by a handful of assistant instructors, inscribed first-circle formations in chalk on the room's enormous blackboard. The twenty-five students of Junior Class C did their best to copy the geometry into their notes, scratching away while Amelia listened in on Kawas’s instruction. “Note the double-helix shouldn’t pass the heartline here,” Kawas intoned to the class, snapping a long cane against the blackboard. “The aetherflow must separate before; otherwise, you won’t have room to construct the dextral and sinistral triquetra here and here.” The instructor prodded at another area of the board, saying, “Those of you who struggle to form first-circle triquetras can use the simpler lemniscate as a replacement, although you’ll struggle to match the former’s efficiency. For the select few in the class who are already experienced with these sub-formations, consider replacing this area with a reuleaux trique...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-Six: In Asamaywa's Shadow</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1984603/chapter-fifty-six-in-asamaywas-shadow</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1984603/chapter-fifty-six-in-asamaywas-shadow</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 20:26:14 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Noburu shivered against the bitter lowland weather. He hugged himself, preserving his body heat, covering the holes in his tattered clothes and hiding the package he carried. He had warmer clothes hidden away, but Noburu didn’t dare wear them outside. Winter was when people got desperate, and if Noburu wanted to keep pretending he was the same as everyone else, he couldn’t afford to be seen as possessing too much wealth. Not that he was wealthy. Noburu, like the majority of the slum-dwellers, was poor . Down here in the narrow streets winding between ramshackle buildings, if your coin purse were seen holding more than a few scraps of copper, it wouldn’t be long before a cutthroat or guard would follow you with less than honourable intentions. Often, they were the same person. It wasn’t a difference in wealth that discriminated Noburu from the rest of the slum. It was his spirit . The people down here had long since given up on a better life. They would beg, steal or otherwise take what...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-Seven: Refinement</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1990373/chapter-fifty-seven-refinement</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1990373/chapter-fifty-seven-refinement</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 19:54:37 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[A fter Amelia left Lunaria’s observatory, she dropped off the book about the Formless in her room before hunting down Serena for some aura training. Given Katalin’s morning session and the events that had transpired, most normal people would baulk at the idea of doing more . However, Amelia’s magic made her an exception to the norm. Even with her body that was supernaturally more resilient due to her game stats, she was sure she would have fallen asleep if it weren't for her healing abilities; she needed a dash of it to repair her wound and recover from her exhaustion. Aseco’s magic was miraculous, but it had its downsides. It prevented her muscles from fully benefitting from the intense training they’d been subjected to. The divine healing simply healed away the damage to the muscles instead of letting her body naturally strengthen the tissue through its normal processes. Finding Serena was easy; even if Amelia didn’t have her flow of aether that powered Serena’s wards to guide her, s...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-Eight: A World War</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1995014/chapter-fifty-eight-a-world-war</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/1995014/chapter-fifty-eight-a-world-war</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:53:12 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena woke to a comforting warmth divided into two parts: the first being the golden-haired Amelia nestled in her arms, snuggling against her chest; the second was the radiant glow of Amelia’s magic enveloping Serena, soothing her muscle soreness and dispelling any lingering sleepiness. She’d experienced the sensation of going from asleep to fully awake in a split second before. Serena had been shelled awake on more than one occasion, and Anathor had done his fair share of acting as an alarm while she’d been asleep in her hammock. What she would never get used to was the magic-induced wakefulness that was on par with adrenaline. “I presume you’re awake?” Serena intoned, bending down and ruffling Amelia’s hair. Seven hells, Amelia smelt good. Her mother once told Serena that the man she’d marry would smell alluring. She didn’t quite understand it until recently. Of course, her mother would never have thought it would be another woman who would be so welcoming to her daughter's nose. Wa...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Fifty-Nine: A Knife In The Night</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2006232/chapter-fifty-nine-a-knife-in-the-night</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2006232/chapter-fifty-nine-a-knife-in-the-night</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 19:59:28 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[With the occasional hiss of steam, the plateau lift continued trundling its way up the cliff face towards Asamaywa. Peering over the railing and looking down, Noburu could see the slums fade away until they merged into one great smear of gloom and grey. As the distance grew, he felt a growing sense of liberation. Living in the slums was a sordid experience; he always felt a little dirty, no matter how much he washed. He somehow felt cleaner by riding the lift and rising above it all. He glanced at the woman next to him. Seonmi stood tall, wearing the uniform Yoshiro provided them both. There was no way the lift guards would’ve allowed them through with how they usually looked, even with a bribe, so they’d been forced to get into character immediately and use their forged travel permits. The guards barely gave them a second look before letting them through. The truth was that as long as you look and act the part, people will naturally assume you are who you say you are. A grimy slum-dwe...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Sixty: Ochimusha</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2011441/chapter-sixty-ochimusha</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2011441/chapter-sixty-ochimusha</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Serena woke to the sound of hurried footsteps in the outside corridor. She immediately knew the owner of those footsteps was coming to communicate bad news. It was the same type of determined strides she’d grown familiar with from her time as a captain. On many occasions, Tomes or Dagon approached her quarters in the Vengeance in the same way, always coming to inform her of a problem. She elbowed Amelia. “Get dressed,” she hissed before climbing out of bed and slipping on her instructor uniform. She barely had time to fix her jacket when the footsteps stopped outside her door and the person behind it rapidly knocked. Judging from the aether signature, it was either Ryosuke or the grandmaster. “A moment!” she called, then frowned realising it was unlikely her shout would be heard through Amelia’s sound-blocking ward. The room brightened, and she turned to see a golden glow with hints of blue fading from Amelia’s body - she had healed herself wide awake. “Instructor Halen?” a voice sound...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Sixty-One: Investigating The Shimmer</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2023981/chapter-sixty-one-investigating-the-shimmer</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2023981/chapter-sixty-one-investigating-the-shimmer</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:14:59 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[The workspace the academy prepared for them was a small room through an unassuming door on the lower floor, away from the main throughway. Once, Noburu thought it might have been a classroom, judging from the inset part of the wall where a large blackboard would have fitted. They were told it had been a nearly forgotten storage room for years until it was hastily tidied and cleaned pending their arrival. The assorted furniture and boxes were piled against one side, and a large table was set up in the remaining space for their work. Hardly the most modern workshop. A few armour sets stood on the table, propped up by their wooden stands. Lying alongside them were half a dozen swords and a few spearheads. Noburu and Seonmi pretended to expertly examine the artefacts while the staff member assigned to show them around watched with mild interest. The demon, a man named Takumi, who didn’t feel like much of a warrior, served as the academy's archivist. “Mmm,” Noburu mumbled, peering through a...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Sixty-Two: Mel's Deductions</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2033074/chapter-sixty-two-mels-deductions</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2033074/chapter-sixty-two-mels-deductions</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 18:21:35 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[Under pressure from Seonmi, the archivist Takumi sought permission from his superior, Noel Yamaguchi, Head of the Department of History and Military Studies. The Department Head's narrow, investigative eyes worried Noburu, but Seonmi’s act as the work-driven Yunseo Yoo-Jung won through, and they got permission for her to explore the storage room for replacement rivets. If anything, he seemed annoyed they’d bothered him with the request. The Department Head reiterated they must remain under guard, and since they could only spare a singular pair of horns to guard them, Noburu and Seonmi had to move together. While Noburu clenched his jaw in annoyance and Seonmi clicked her tongue, it was actually the ideal outcome. This way, they could both explore the storage under the guise of Seonmi searching for replacement metal. The storage facility was a large basement filled with old boxes and crates. Takumi explained that while many of the items had been stored here for decades, the room itself ...]]&gt;</description></item><item><title>Chapter Sixty-Three: Noburu's Experience</title><link>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2038690/chapter-sixty-three-noburus-experience</link><guid>https://www.royalroad.com/fiction/92080/amelia-thornheart/chapter/2038690/chapter-sixty-three-noburus-experience</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 20:56:07 +0000</pubDate><description>&lt;![CDATA[It was time for Noburu to finish the job. He and Seonmi made their final plans in their rented accommodation. Their charisma and skills had paid off; not only had they gotten an impression of the key they needed, which they used to create a replica via a contact Seonmi knew, but they also managed to identify the exact box containing the target artefact. Why would a pair of old daggers be worth so much, anyway? “Are you sure your ability can last?” Seonmi asked, blinking at him with her brilliant blood-orange eyes. “It’ll take at least ten minutes. Every breath you take will exhaust you.” “It’s easier in the city. I’ll manage it,” Noburu affirmed. He’d tested his blessing enough to know it was mostly the presence of the ghost plants that exhausted him. Down in the slums, the ghostworld was full of ethereal plant life, but up here in the city, it was less present. Something about demon activity and the presence of aetherlights discouraged their spread. They reviewed their plan one more t...]]&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>